你已经实现了主activity的线框构架。那么现在让我们来
You've implemented the main activity wireframe. So, now, we can move
实现子activity的事件框架。这就是它的实现图。
on to the detail activity wireframe. This is what it looks
这有日期、最高最低气温，
like. We have the date, the high and low temperatures, and
还有补充的天气信息。我们还有天气图像和天气预报。
then additional weather information. We also have the weather icon and
这些水平对齐。
the weather forecast. And these line up horizontally. Build up the
我们在layout XML里构建线框布局。然后对你所填充的信息
layout XML for this wireframe. Then modify the detail fragments that
和新视图进行细节上的修改。
you can populate all this information, including these new views. While
当如上操作时，你可以把这块代码移动到自己的文件里，
you're doing that, you might as well move the detail fragment
让它独立于具体的activity。
into its own file, so it's separate from the detail activity. At
当你把它移到自己的文件里时，这个类就可以写的很长。
this point the detail fragment class is getting pretty long so you can
在开始之前，我想说，
move that into it its own file. Before you get started, I want
这里的布局信息会占用了大量的垂直空间。
to point out that this layout has information taking up a lot of
当你旋转设备切换成横屏，说者换成一个跟应用程序显示不一致的设备时，
vertical space. If you rotate your device into landscape mode, or you have
布局中以一些内容就可能被隔断。
a smaller height device, some of the content could get cut off. So
那么我们想个办法让布局可以垂直滚动。
think about how you can make this layout be vertically scrollable. To show
给大家说一下我的想法，我添加了一对多文本行在布局的底部。
you what I mean, I added a couple more lines of text at
接下来设置内容垂直滚动，
the bottom of the layout. Then I made the content vertically scrollable
这样你们就能看到全部内容了。
so you can see all the information. So go ahead and make that
继续，也改变你的布局吧。当你完成以上步骤时，
change to your layout as well. When you're done with all these
你的app会是这样。现在，我们并不关心
steps, this is what the app should look like. We don't care about
画面的细节效果。我们只是要确保功能实现，
the visual details now. We just want to make sure the functionality is
能将所有信息正确的显示在屏幕上。
hooked up, so all the right information is displayed on screen. You can
你可以使用下面提供的代码，
use the code snippets provided below
来帮助你的函数和字符串。
for helper functions and strings that you're
现在留一个占位图，会对接下来的开发有好处。
going to need. And again, leaving a placeholder image is fine for now